# **Aidan Johnson**

Spring 2024 Graduate

Skilled Programmer with over 4 years of C ++ programming experience. Logical and passionate professional with excellent problem-solving and time management skills. Team player dedicated to continuing education within the computer programming and gaming sector. Highly motivated programmer with experience in C++, Java, C#, and Python.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Supplemental Instructor -** *University of Houston, Victoria, TX* 

02/2021 - PRESENT

- Coached learning developers on best practices in C++ programming, enhancing individual capabilities and productivity.
- Improved student retention through tailored one-on-one tutoring sessions for struggling individuals.
- Led several sessions with small groups to encourage communication and improve interpersonal relationships.
- Addressed common misconceptions and knowledge gaps during instruction sessions.

Games Attendant - Main Event Entertainment, San Antonio, TX

03/2017 - 01/2018

- Assisted in revenue generation through efficient handling of game transactions, including cash handling and prize distribution.
- Utilized effective communication skills when interacting with both guests and teammates, fostering positive relationships.
- Maintained a safe environment for guests by ensuring proper use of equipment and adherence to safety guidelines for Laser Tag and Gravity Ropes course.

## **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelors of Science in Digital Gaming and Simulation**

University of Houston, Victoria, TX

08/2019 - Current

- Accomplished student in Digital Gaming and Simulation, maintaining a 3.549 cumulative GPA
- Ran TTPRG campaigns in multiple RPG systems that apply practices learned in courses

**High School Graduate -** Roosevelt High School, San Antonio, TX

- Graduate of DATA Magnet Program
- Received multiple commendations and awards including 4 time recipient of PICK Award, Excellence in Video Game Design, and Excellence in Animation

San Antonio, TX 78258
Open to Relocation
(210) 862-8868
aidanjohnson151@gmail.com
My Portfolio

#### **SKILLS**

Object-Oriented
Programming
Strong Algorithm Knowledge
Programming Languages
Designing Core Gameplay

## **CODING LANGUAGES**

## **Advanced:**

Content

C++

### Intermediate:

C#

Java

Python

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

#### Dean's List

Spring 2020

Fall 2021

Spring & Fall 2022

Spring 2023

## **President's List**

Fall 2020

Fall 2023